David M. Padilla

Full Stack Web Developer

Over 5+ years of experience establishing personal relationships through communications as well as strong analytical skills for interpreting documentation and data to resolve conflicts. Successful in working both team and self-directed settings. Up-and-coming Full Stack Web Developer ready to make an impact in designing and simplifying the complexities of your applications.

Personal Info

Address

717 Royal Anne Lane Raleigh, NC 27615

Phone

+1 919 869 9647

Email

davidpadilla.dev@gmail.com

Website

davidpadilla.io

GitHub

github.com/dpadillajs

LinkedIn

Mongoose

linkedin.com/in/davidmpadilla

Technologies

recimologies	
HTML5	Excellent
CSS3	Excellent
Bootstrap 4	Advanced
JavaScript	Advanced
jQuery	Excellent
Handlebars	Advanced
React	Intermediate
Node.js	Intermediate
Express	Intermediate
Firebase	Basic
MySQL	Intermediate
Sequelize	Intermediate
MongoDB	Intermediate

Intermediate

Experience

2018-02 - Financial Associate I - Health & Welfare

2018-09

Fidelity Investments

- Analyzed thousands of IBM employee records and documentation to troubleshoot health-related requests.
- Solved critical setbacks through positive verbiage, empathy, and ownership.
- Provided administrative support to manager through peer mentorship and procedural write-ups.
- Won multiple awards for driving positive call interactions and exceptional review scores.

2017-08 - Customer Service Representative

2018-01

Veritude

- Contracted through Fidelity's temporary staffing agency to provide operational support to IBM employees.
- Converted to permanent position within six months for exceptional metrics in call efficiency and customer feedback.

2014-01 - Scheduling Agent

2017-07

AIG VALIC

- Scheduled thousands of meaningful appointments for over 35+ financial advisors across the Mid-Atlantic Region.
- Reestablished communication between advisors and their clients, which in turn resulted in increases to their monthly contributions as well as greater client retention.
- Helped one advisor significantly add over a quarter million in assets from multiple discovery meetings, which was then managed through the company.
- Created new departmental procedures, systems, and statistical databases through Excel for productivity awareness to increase performance from both the scheduling staff and supervisor.

Education

2005-08 - East Chapel Hill High School

2009-06 HS Diploma

2018-10 - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

2019-04 Professional Certificate, UNC Coding Bootcamp

References

Jordan Hensley

UNC Coding Bootcamp, Trilogy Education Teacher Assistant (540) 309-6624

Heather Williamson

Fidelity Investments

Manager DB/HW

(702) 412-5115